(Sheldon:)I lost a bet to Wolowitz.
(Leonard:)-You're saying you talked to Penny?
-Yes.
(Sheldon:)-Interesting.
-Hardly.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)Have I crossed
some sort of line again?
(Leonard:)Little bit.
(Howard:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Who cares?
(Penny:)-Oh, hey.
-Hey, what did Sheldon say to you?
Not a lot. That we always have the
option of going back to being friends.
(Leonard:)-Is that what you want?
-I don't know.
(Penny:)I mean, you have to admit...
(Penny:)...things seemed simpler
when we were just friends.
(Leonard:)I guess.
(Penny:)-It would take the pressure off.
-It would, wouldn't it?
(Penny:)So we'll just be friends.
(Leonard:)Good. Good.
(Penny:)Come here.
[BOTH MOANING]
(Leonard:)Okay-dokay.